I'm Yuu Yamazaki, 16 years old, from Aichi, Japan. My favorite Nobita's classmate is Abarayakun.
I'm from Aichi prefecture, where people put miso on everything they cook.
In my family, there is always miso in the fridge called "dipping miso".
Miso?
Yes, my favorite thing to put miso on oden is to put miso on oden.
Hello, my partner this time.
Yuhane Yamazaki of Ami Morikawa of Beyond's Rain
and Shiori Nishida from Beyond's Subway!
We are going to be sharing with you this time.
Please stay with us until the end.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
This will be the last show before I graduate from Halo! Sta. MC before my graduation.
I remember my voice was so quiet when I debuted.
I remember my voice was very quiet when I was a debutante, but I was surprised to hear you speak so clearly and clearly.
You were talking a lot.
I thought she was doing her best.
We started with Ihane, who is 16 years old.
I had heard that Ihane was very nervous when she was filming the show.
I could feel her nervousness, but every word she said was really interesting.
It made me happy.
I think she is a wonderful girl.
Myons released a new single "High to Diamond Go City Go Hook" on the 29th of last month.
We had a live release event and the music is very cool!
The music this time is very cool
Hi To Diamond is a very cool song.
It's so cool!
Each member's charm and coolness that has not been known before has been found by many people.
I'm so happy that so many people are discovering the charm and coolness of each member that has not been known before.
I'm so happy!
At the release events, I usually hear people say, "I like Miyons, but I'm pushing for Shiori Nishida the most.
I think it would be great if we could have a farewell party at the release event to talk with the people who are supporting me and pushing other people.
I wish it was at a release event or a send-off party, but yes, it was at that time.
I was so happy to hear from them, and I was so glad to know that you were there.
It was a great event that made me feel that everyone was thinking about me like that.
It was a great event and I was able to feel that everyone was thinking that way.
Now please take a look at this video.
The show is about to begin, but I'm not sure if I'm in the right frame of mind or not,
I'm feeling very organized in my mind, and I'm thinking that this will be my last performance with Mr. Umemura,
I don't know how it will turn out,
But this is the last show of the tour, and I've had a lot of fun on this tour,
I really want to make today the most enjoyable performance of the tour,
I will do my best to enjoy the show.
I will do my best.
I am really nervous because it is Uemura-san's graduation performance, and I feel like I really don't know what to do right now, but I will enjoy this nervousness as well,
I will only have one voice,
I will do my best.
Afuri, Une, Hime, Mimi, Ai, Ichikori, Kisaki, Sakira, Akari, Mifu
Yes, so here we are today,
I am very happy to be able to spend such an important moment with everyone at the time of graduation,
I am very, very happy to be able to spend such an important moment with everyone at the time of graduation.
I have many memories of the past 11 years,
I cherish the present moment, so I hope to enjoy and make the best of it with everyone,
I hope everyone can enjoy and make memories with me in the present, so please have confidence and make many memories that will give you confidence today.
Friday night we can get out of here.
Are you ready?
If you're not ready, Bye bye
Time is not as it seems
Won't come from a dream
The starry sky is dazzling tonight
You can hold me, you can hold me, you can hold me
If I were a dream, I'd do it
One of a girl, two of a girl ni
Society is cool, the fashion is already crew
The starry sky is dazzling tonight
You can be nice to me, you can be nice to me
I wish I'd been told
Girl's tears, girl's anxiety
I'm the girl who doesn't notice One thing I can't stop
You are in better perspective
Hang in there
BEYONES Rain Forest Up the River with Yuu Yamazaki
and Shioli Nishida of Beyones Subway, Halo! stay!
From here, I'd like to tell you a little bit about each other.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so don't think too much and answer them quickly.
Okay, I'll do my best.
Shiori Nishida celebrated her 21st birthday on the 7th of this month.
What are your ambitions for your 21st birthday?
To make many people smile.
Please tell us about your memories of the Tokaido Shinkansen in connection with your new song "Go City Go.
Hand towels in the green car
In reference to the lyrics of the new song "High to Diamond", what is the moment when you recently got burned out?
When the birthday event was over.
Thank you for your hard work
To those of us who are trainee classmates
Only Shiori Nishida knows
I, Yuhayame Yamazaki, have a surprising side to me
Surprisingly, I don't shed tears
The Hello Project song you want to sing with me is
Sad Heaven by Cute
Thank you very much.
I've been wondering about a lot of things...
Happy Birthday to you!
Thank you very much.
Twenty-one years old.
Yes, I'm 21, and we're the same age now.
We're the same age now.
How do you feel now that you're 21?
Nothing's changed.
That's right.
But June is going to be a very busy month for me, so I have to make the most of every second of every day.
I'm thinking that I have to make the most of every second of every day.
I'd like to make the most of every second of every day.
I'd like to sing a song from Hello Project with you.
Mr. Kiyota's "Sad Heaven
I've got it.
Here it is.
This song is
I sang this song at a FC event called "Futari wa Yuhashi
I sang this song at a franchise event called "Futari wa Yubashi
I wanted to sing it one more time.
I want to sing it again.
I want to practice a lot.
I want to sing again with my voice properly matched.
It will be different from then, won't it?
I'm sure it will be in a few years when I can sing again.
I think I would like to sing again in a few years, but if it comes true someday, it will be in a few years.
It's a dream that I would like to fulfill someday.
I'm happy to hear that.
Questions for Ihane-chan after the VTR
Haloset Beyond High 2 Diamond Now on sale
Beyond High GO!Now on sale!
Gold metal power up!
I want to unleash it!
Let's go! BEYOND BEYOND BEYOND BEYOND
Self!
Another day of departure
Now on sale!
Juice Jutsu! Concert Tour 2024
Manrai Web's Academy Millstones Special is over!
I'm so happy. I'm sure there will be plenty more to come for the four of us after this.
It's that much fun!
I thought the concert was like a reward for all kinds of thoughts.
So, you know, I was very happy to be able to make a video of it, and I was very happy too.
Now I would like to ask you, how about you, Sakura-chan?
Yes, during the performance, I started to feel the reality of the event and I cried a lot.
But now that it's over and I'm spending my time like this...
I didn't feel that much that I had graduated.
The concert itself was so much fun.
It was dozens of times more enjoyable than the usual Budokan concert.
I wonder if you are really graduating,
I was able to deliver Mr. Uemura's graduation to me without regret,
I sometimes messed up the words,
I regret it very much,
But after that, I regret it already!
But I was happy!
Congratulations, Ringo.
Ringo-chan.
I told Mr. Kamimura a long time ago before I called him to sing that I would not cry anymore,
You cried at all on this tour.
So I tried not to cry at all on this tour,
I came here not to cry, so I cried a lot today.
I cried a lot.
You cried a lot.
That's great, great.
And, there were people who cried like sisters after the show, and there were people who cried like sisters after the show,
Oh, you were there?
They were like sisters, too.
That's amazing.
I thought, "That's amazing.
I had stopped the show, but why was there such an outpouring of people? That's how the tension started.
It was the strangest thing.
I had made up my mind, I had made up my mind.
I had decided that I would feel the loneliness until the end of the show, and that I would only feel the enjoyment now,
I was looking at the camera, thinking, "I can feel the loneliness until the end of the show, so I will only feel the joy now,
I was looking at the camera, thinking, "I can feel the loneliness until the end of the show, so now I can only feel the fun.
But I feel the same way.
I also said that I would not shed a tear during the performance.
I thought we were going to do it.
I was going to encourage each other.
Actually, it was like we were brothers.
Yes, that's right.
It's getting a little crazy, so I'll give it back.
I'll give it back. I'm not going to give anything back even if they give it back to me.
Well, the concert was a lot of things like this,
How was Lulu?
It was the concert where I received the baton of the leader,
I think it was a concert that I will never forget in my heart,
I wanted all JuiceJuice fans to be filled with emotion,
We also wanted the JuiceJuice fans to be full of emotion, so we had a big explosion, and there were members who did various takes and so on,
I thought it was cool to see the growth of the members,
I would like to continue to do my best with JuiceJuice, and I look forward to your continued support.
Thank you very much for your continued support.
That's all for JuiceJuice.
Bye bye.
Next, I would like to ask Yuhane a question.
Please do.
Tell me Yuhane's law after the law of the book.
If you talk to me, I will break out of my shell.
It's been about 8 years since we joined the traineeship together.
Tell me your best memory with me, Shiori Nishida.
It's when we did a duet at the Hina Fest.
What is the biggest change in yourself in the 6 years since you joined BEYONES?
I have become more confident.
What is your favorite costume in BEYONES?
Well, the costume of the boy with glasses.
What is the secret tool of Doraemon that you think is perfect for you right now?
Doraemon's secret tool... the Dokodemo Dore.
Thank you very much.
It's the royal road.
You're on the high road.
What's the most recent visit?
Well, one day ago.
Yes, a day ago.
I'm sure you'll want to see everyone.
I'm going to use the "Door Anywhere" to meet everyone.
That's what you mean.
That's nice.
I'm going to meet them.
I'm coming to see you.
Be on your guard.
Don't let your guard down.
Wait for me.
Be on your guard.
Don't let your guard down, and I'll show up suddenly.
Please look forward to it
My fondest memory with Shori Nishida
Playing Rio at the Hina Fest.
Lottery
At HinaFes, we had a lottery to decide the shuffle unit.
Yes, it's a standard event.
There's the usual thing, but it's hard to guess the winner by lottery.
Yes, I heard it's limited. It's fate, isn't it, that we can both guess the same date, the same performance date?
It's fate, you know. I was really surprised.
When I saw the name written on the board, I was so shocked that I couldn't stop shaking.
I was so happy to know that we could do it together.
I was so happy, and I really felt the ocean.
I'm so happy that we were able to do it together.
I'm glad we were able to do it together.
I wonder if I dropped it somewhere in the starry sky.
I don't know who I'm going to meet... or what's waiting for me there...
I don't know who I'm going to meet or what's waiting for me
I'm not shining bright
A new morning, my heart is thumping
Yeah, the tailwind is blowing, my cheeks are up in the air, my heart's in an uproar
I'm driving through, I've raised my reforms
Only a dazzling premonition to the crowd
Billions of light years away
Understanding will be my path
I believe
Pray on my own
I believeWait for my
Always a wave of color for hope
I can go anywhere
We have some memories
We have some memoriesMemories
Who are we going to see, what's waiting for us, do we need a reason for our rising passion?
In the universe behind my eyelids, I only hear the echoing voice
Softly, deep down, it's calling
Hey, I've carved out a new morning in the distance, the rust that makes my heart pound
Hey I raised my cheeks again and again
The panorama shimmering in golden colors
The horizon is shimmering beautiful
The scenery that even my breath takes me I feel it
Way over my head
If only I could see the dazzling highlights now
I don't need my own place
I try to believe in it, I repeat it so much that I forget
That light becomes my path
I feel me
Only a dazzling premonition in the crowd
What is invalid and goes to the other side
The light becomes my path
I feel it
Even if I lose my heart in a rainstorm
I'll find you again and again
I light up the journey far and wide, but I'll still find it again and again
I light up the journey far and wide
Breathe as a memories
Every time I get lost, you see, I'm leading the way
In Osaka
I was given dance lessons as a trainee in the Kansai region.
I've been teaching dance lessons as a trainee in the Kansai region since then, and it's been 14 years now.
I'm surprised again.
After that, various things happened.
I decided to take lessons in Tokyo with the Halo Pro trainees.
I took the wrong transit several times, even though it was a fixed route
I got lost.
I think that many people have guided me to this point.
Whoever saw me at that time
I don't think anyone could have predicted that she would become the leader of Juice Juice.
I'm very, very proud of her.
Very, very, very
very, very naive
JuiceJuice has given me a new path in my life.
including TSUNKU and all the staff
and
friends who supported me
my family
And JuiceJuice family
And all the members
I really feel that
Everyone is very important to me.
I've been surrounded by my four sisters since we formed the group
I've been surrounded by my four older sisters since we formed the group
shoulder to shoulder in a row
One year and four months
We also had a chance to do a live concert in a year and 4 months, and we had a chance to go around the world in a year and a half,
I will always treasure this experience with my precious members and JuiceJuice family members for the rest of my life.
I will treasure it forever.
And after that, they joined JuiceJuice and became our new members.
When we were performing live, I promised myself that I would not have any negative feelings.
I promised not to bring any negativity to the stage.
I was enjoying the stage.
I didn't have to tell them that in words.
They took the initiative and surrounded JuiceJuice with smiles.
Thank you so much!
And I think it was because I met Juice Juice that one of my idols, who had been living a life of a spineless person, was able to change.
Mr. Tsunku writes very strong lyrics for Juice Juice.
I think we naturally became stronger and tougher by watching him write them.
That's what I've been saying.
I think that's where the strength and freedom of Juice Juice came from.
This tour title one line
The thought that went into it is
Juice Juice is called Juice Juice
I mean, juice juice equals juice juice.
but it also means "juice juice is juice juice".
Juice Juice is juice juice.
I wondered what I could leave behind in Juice Juice.
Two years ago, when I became a leader, I thought about what I could leave behind in Juice Juice.
I thought about what I could leave behind in Juice Juice, like an equal in the middle of the juice.
I thought it would be nice if I could be the one to connect the future,
I have put everything I have into this project.
The symbol "equal" is a parallel and equal symbol,
I heard that the symbol "equal" was created because it is a parallel line and equal to any other line.
We are not just one line, but another JuiceJuice.
As another JuiceJuice family line
I really feel that we are not in one line but in another JuiceJuice family line
I am really reassured to think that we are not just one line
I think that you are the kind of existence that will continue to support us in the future.
What I have said here
And what I couldn't say
I'd like to say that I love Juice Juice and I'd like to thank you for everything.
Juice Juice's favorite
I love Juice Juice.
I've been through a lot in my 11 years
I've tasted the sweet and the sour, but at the end of the day.
But in the end, the only thing that remains is a feeling of happiness... thank you for giving me JuiceJuice, a path of hope.
And the origin of my name, Akari
I hope that I can follow the bright path and light it up forever
That was the origin of my name.
If I had not experienced this idol experience
I would not have been able to appreciate the origin of my name so much.
My first complex was my smile.
The reason why I started to like smiling
While spending time with JuiceJuice family members
I think it is one of the weapons that I have come to love.
I will continue to use it as my weapon
I would like to continue to be a person who can give back to your smiles
I would like to continue to be a person who can give back to your smiles.
I would like to thank you for loving JuiceJuice and for finding JuiceJuice.
and for finding JuiceJuice.
Thank you for finding JuiceJuice.
I'm cheering for you so that you can live a sparkling life from tomorrow
I'm cheering for you so that you can live a sparkling everyday life from tomorrow onwards.
I love you so much!
Thank you so much.
I was so nervous.
Thank you very much.
Wow, I was nervous. Thank you very much.
me
memeBeyond Rainy Morikawa Umi's Yuu Yamazaki and
Beyond Subway's Shiori Nishida presents Halo! sta.
Tomorrow, June 27th at Toyosu Pit.
Beyond Live Tour 2024 Spring
Personality OF DREAMS will take place!
Yes, this time I would like to talk to Yuhane about a few things in preparation for her graduation!
Thank you very much.
As trainees, are you aware of any aspects of the group you're in now that you've joined?
I'm very aware of it. I'm always aware of it.
I'm always aware of you, like I'm always looking at you sideways like this, but really
If it were not for Nishida, I would not have been able to do so well
I don't want to lose the most
We joined at the same time.
Seeing her hard work was an inspiration to me
And also gave me a lot of courage
Courage? Really?
Yes, I did!
When the group was first formed.
Nishi-chan raised his hand
When you raised your hand and gave your opinion to everyone.
I was like, "I didn't know you could do that.
He was so surprised at the beginning, even though we were all in the same group.
He started talking on his own.
I felt a little left out there.
I'm not the type of person who likes to talk like that.
I can't win there anymore.
I'm really
I'm glad.
That's why I feel like I can do my best.
I see. I see.
I'm, like, yuh-huh.
You're a person whose beliefs really carry through. Belief.
That's why Yuhane has always had her ideal idol image, or something like that,
She has always had this image of her ideal idol, or something like that, and she has been quietly working hard to achieve it.
Yuhane has always had this image of an ideal idol, and she has been working hard to achieve it.
She has a cool, manly appearance.
I really respect him for that.
Thank you very much.
I made my major debut at a beauty salon.
August is the 5th anniversary.
Is there a moment that you feel was a turning point?
But only in a beauty salon. It's a stage, isn't it?
Oh, the stage, yes, indeed.
I was given a very important role in a play called "The Palace of the Left and Right Beauties.
I also got a very important role in my very first play, Alice and Her Friends in Wonderland.
But at that time, it was my first time too much.
I was relying on everyone around me.
Beauty Festival Palace
This time, I felt like I had to lead the way again.
But I'm not the type of person who can do that kind of thing.
I didn't want to show my uneasiness.
He said, "I'm fine, so just follow me.
He didn't say it in words, but...
But he really did.
I thought that if I kept a positive attitude
I thought that if I was positive, the stage itself would have a positive atmosphere.
I was trying my best to imagine that, and I was right.
I was really happy that Yuha Yamazaki was so strong in the role, and she spent all the time backstage and behind the scenes during the rehearsal period.
I was 20 years old, and I longed to be 20 years old.
I was 20, but I was only 19. I was thinking about what I wanted to do when I turned 20.
You were thinking about that?
I'd like to hear how you started thinking about the next stage of Haloloste.
Well, I was inspired by the talented Miyons members around me.
They really pushed me to go on this path.
If I had been in a state of uncertainty in the past, I probably wouldn't have made the decision.
I probably would not have made the decision.
I want to say thank you to the Beyoncés.
When I first announced to the members that I was graduating
Yuhane said
This situation is very warm and comfortable for me.
But I want to continue to grow.
I'm going to leave this place and do my best.
It was really cool that he made the decision to leave his comfortable place.
I was really moved by it.
But really, I'm very comfortable here.
Beyoncé.
I get it.
I guess we'll see.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, we will.
I'll see you in the future.
I'll see you.
All of us.
All of us. - All of us.
A lot.
What kind of expression would you like to work on in the future?
Yes, I do.
What I have learned so far in Hello Project
What I have learned in Hello Project
I would like to turn it into confidence
I'll be able to use what I've learned
I would like to spread my favorite songs
I would like to spread my favorite songs more and more.
Lastly, I would like to say
Lastly, to my fans
To the audience
To those who are coming to the graduation performance
Please give a message to those who are coming to the graduation performance.
Thank you so much for your support.
Thank you so much!
You have given me so much power and energy
I really can't count how much power and energy
I've received so much power and energy from all of you every day.
I really love you all!
I want to convey that feeling to you at tomorrow's performance to the extent that you will be surprised.
I will do my best until the end.
I'm Yuu Yamazaki from Halostaye, Beyonds Rainy River Sea and Shiori Nishida from Beyonds Subway.
It's time to say goodbye to you all!
It's time to say goodbye!
Wow!
For the last time
I'm really glad that we were able to MC together.
I'm really glad
I was so happy
Graduation is coming up
By the time it's being distributed
I can really feel the day after.
I can really feel it.
Recently, I've been working without Yuhane.
I've heard that she's working on a photo shoot.
When I see her presenting me with a bouquet of flowers, it makes me realize how close we really are.
I want to cherish the time we can spend together.
I'm so happy.
MC at the end
With Shiori Nishida
I was so happy to be able to talk about various things with her.
I was so happy to be able to talk with her and
Through this MC for Halostei, I learned the power of
I learned a lot about the power of MCing
I will continue to do so in the future.
As a viewer
I'm looking forward to it.
Here's an announcement!
BEYOND 5th single
High to Diamond Go City Go
Hook's Law is now available
Including the addtion tracks.
All of the songs are wonderful, so please listen to them as much as you can!
Please listen to them!
Thank you very much!
BEYOND LIVE T 2024 Spring Personality Wings of Dreams will be held tomorrow, June 27.
This will be broadcast live and live viewing will be available nationwide, so please come and watch it.
And on July 13, Hello Project 2024 Summer Maor of Asleaga Altair will start!
It has been a long time since we had a concert with the whole group, so we will do our best.
Haloste is a channel where Hello Project members will be appearing more and more!
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please give us a high rating and subscribe to our channel!
Please give us a high rating, comment, and subscribe to our channel. This time, we had BEYOND'S Rain Forest, Kawao Mino, Yamazaki Yuha, and BEYOND'S Tsukatetsu's Nishida Shiori.
Farewell.
Now, here is the really, really last song. Since that day when I opened that door of my dream
How many seasons have come?
I wipe with a towel of sweat, I keep my tears in my heart, MEME
me
me me me me, it looked a little different.
That's when, yes.
That's when my real time began to move.
Get it together!
Smile and say you see the finish line
Smile and say it's not the goal
Let's still look for it
Wow Wow Wow
If you believe in it, it will come true
Wishin' on you and the blue sky
I've made it this far
Wow, wow, wow, wow
I was lost at the crossroads
Baby Baby Baby
I'll be with you tomorrow
How many years has it been?
How many times I almost lost
I always asked myself.
Is this a turning point? Or is it just a passing phase?
Maybe it's up to me.
Alone in the corner of my room
I counted the smiles and the tears.
A smile, yes, even a little one
And the world at large shines brighter
Crying, "Where's the goal?
Crying that there's no finish line
I looked up at the clouds
Wow, wow, wow
I'm looking at where is tomorrow
All I can see are the memories
There's still so much more I can do
Wow, wow, wow, wow
There's no answer at the crossroads
Baby Baby Baby
Tomorrow's that way
I won't give up, no matter how far we go, let's all run together
Keep the goal in sight
Laughing when you say you see the finish line Laughing when you say it's not the finish line
Let's keep on looking for it
Oh oh oh oh, if you believe in it, it will come true
I wished for you and the blue sky and we made it this far
Oh Oh Oh Oh, where's the goal, I cry
Crying that there is no finish line
I looked up at the clouds
Wow Wow Wow Wow
Wondering where tomorrow will be
All I could see were the memories
I could still go on
Wow, wow, wow
Somewhere there's a crossroads that hasn't fallen
Baby Baby Baby
Which way is tomorrow?
Tomorrow we'll be together
Tomorrow it's that way
My Alses... my Alses...
My Alses
My Alses.
And I don't know what's wrong with her expression.
What's this?
It's okay to cry.
It's okay to cry. It's okay to cry.
I've been a little busy, you know, with everything.
I'm so happy.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
I absolutely love JuiceJuice from now on.
You love JuiceJuice?
Yes, I just love JuiceJuice.
So I just love JuiceJuice. So I love JuiceJuice.
I understand.
Akari
Rei
Yume
Riai
Ritiko
wise man
Akaki
SAKURO
Akari
Mifu
I will continue to enjoy Jujus Juice too!
We are Jujus.
Yay!
Thank you.
Me, thank you.
I, Akari Uemura, am JuiceJuice!
Thank you!
I, Akari Uemura, would like to thank you for the graduation performance on June 14, which was a condensation of the best parts of JuiceJuice's current body of work, and also a condensation of the best parts of JuiceJuice's history, not just the present.
It was not only the present, but also a condensed version of JuiceJuice's history.
I hope everyone had a great time at the live.
I hope you all really enjoyed the show.
JuiceJuice has always been a group that loves to perform live.
I am very happy to have experienced the graduation with so many people watching over us.
I am very, very happy to have experienced the graduation with so many people watching over us.
Thank you very much for your support.